<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on India 2 Manchester</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on India 2 Manchester</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 16:34:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Waiting Game</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/the-waiting-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 16:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/the-waiting-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting unemployed in FM24-especially with no coaching badges-means nobody will really pick you up. I knew that from previous experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So it became a game of hitting Continue and waiting for the managers to fall. Cold-blooded, I know, but in this game of managers you need to have that edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And eventually it did-Twice:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Screenshot 2025-08-10 210102.png&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/Screenshot%202025-08-10%20210102.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Screenshot 2025-08-10 210119.png&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/Screenshot%202025-08-10%20210119.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These 2 clubs were at the very bottom of the I-League which is India&amp;rsquo;s 2nd divison and in danger of being relegated to the 3rd tier so they need a relegation specialist(Think defend and counter and nothing else). Hardly glamourous but beggars can&amp;rsquo;t be choosers. I had to apply for both of them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ambitious Plan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/an-ambitious-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/an-ambitious-plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have become such a humongous FM24 nut lately. Especially after the next iteration was cancelled. I have been watching a journeyman save on YouTube recently which had me hooked even more. And I also realize that I have never EVER been interested in a journeyman save. My most recent save was starting unemployed in England and after 3 clubs I was at Manchester United one of my favorite clubs ever:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
